kalam.tv 2012-03-24

# Privacy Policy - Kalam

**Updated as of 11 March 2009**

جوجل سياسة الخصوصية يصف كيف مجموعات والشركات التابعة لها التعامل مع المعلومات الشخصية عند استخدام خدمات غوغل

#### Personal Information

  * **Browsing Kalam** You can watch videos on YouTube without having a YouTube Account or a Google Account. You can also contact us through the YouTube Help Centre or by emailing us directly, without having to register for an account. 
  * **Your Kalam Account.** For some activities on YouTube, such as uploading videos, posting comments, flagging videos or watching restricted videos, you need a YouTube or Google Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorised access. A Google Account, additionally, allows you to access other Google services that require registration.
  * **Usage Information.** When you use YouTube, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the channels, groups and favourites to which you subscribe, which other users you communicate with, the videos that you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers and information that you display about yourself, as well as information that you click in YouTube (including UI elements, settings). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your YouTube Account. In order to ensure the quality of our service to you, we may place a tag (also called a "web beacon") in HTML-based customer support emails or other communications with you in order to confirm delivery. 
  * **Content Uploaded to Site**. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g. video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others. If you download the YouTube Uploader, your copy includes a unique application number. This number and information about your installation of the Uploader (version number, language) will be sent to YouTube when the Uploader automatically checks for updates and will be used to update your version of the Uploader.

#### Privacy

  * If you submit personal information to YouTube, we may use that information to operate, maintain and improve the features and functionality of YouTube, and to process any flagging activity or other communication that you send to us. 
  * We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major YouTube changes or for customer service purposes). You can also choose how often YouTube sends you email updates in your YouTube Account settings page. 
  * We use cookies, web beacons and log-file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time that you visit YouTube; (b) provide custom, personalised content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions and status in promotions, sweepstakes and contests. 

#### Information That is Publicly Available

  * When you create a YouTube Account, some information about your YouTube Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of YouTube. This may include the date that you opened your YouTube Account, the date that you last logged in to your YouTube Account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of videos that you have watched. 
  * Your YouTube Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on YouTube, such as when you upload videos or send messages through YouTube. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.
